

CV

Name: Seán Werner Year of birth: 1994

Profile

Seán holds a **Higher Vocational Education in Java Development** and has worked as an application developer with a long history of technical know-how (**5+ years**). Worked in an AGILE environment. Extensive experience using GIT Bash to maintain repositories.

Seáns friends characterize him as an exceptionally sociable, cheerful, and supportive individual with a genuine and caring nature. During his free time, he enjoys building his own PC, developing games, painting figures and hiking with his close friends and family.

Tools in assignments: ASP.Net/C#, Unity, Git, AWS.

Work Experience

Application Developer, Diá tom os AB

June 2022 - Dec 2023

Project based system and software development with simulation for scaffolding generation around 3D models of imported houses.

Working in an AGILE environment, the main responsibilities are:

- Developing tools to generate 3D environments with varied heights on hills and holes for the purpose of testing construction objects on unstable terrain, also generating scaffolding around 3D models.
- Working in an AGILE environment with daily Scrum meetings for planning 1-2 week sprints.
- Maintaining the Unit Testing for the application, such as manual and automated tests, while maintaining the core repository.
- Developing price/quantity calculations in-app functionality to also speak with the database through API.
- Creating user friendly UI that is both for advanced and new users.
- Supported DevOps with Continuous Integration and Continuous Deployment of said application.

Tech: ASP.NET, Unity, Gitlab, C#, JavaScript, Git, AWS

Facility Management

April 2018 - June 2022

Maintained facility through technical or electrical means Main responsibilities:

O a same I. Ta alaminia a a /Flan

- General Technician/Electrician.
- Electrical/Chemical Waste management.
- Hold emergency drill lectures.
- General maintenance of the facility.

Backend Support, Sykes Telenor

April 2015 - November 2018

Customer support, call center, backend support for the customer support, this role needed a deep technical understanding of the support software.

Main responsibilities:

- Provide customer support.
- Provide technical help to other customer support colleagues

Negotiate phone contracts with customers

Soldier - Tank Mechanic, Swedish Armed Forces

August 2014 - April 2015

He enlisted for basic military training which eventually led to specialized training in mechanical work for tanks.

Main skills learned:

- Calm under pressure, team leading.
- Social Awareness, Social Structure, Team Building
- Vehicle Mechanic

Education & Courses

Java Development

The focus of the education is to learn object-oriented programming and solve complex problems with Java. Here, you learn to create applications that can reliably run on multiple platforms and components for web development. Other areas you learn include testing, database management, integration, web services, etc. You learn how system development works and how the process of system development is carried out. You also cover the basics of Spring Boot and Java EE, making the education directly targeted towards companies.

Graduation:

- Basic & Advanced Java Development
- Tools & Environments
- Database & Database Administration
- Clean & Testable Code (TDD)

Tech:

Java, SQL, JavaScript, HTML/CSS

Other: Docker, Json, Jenkins, Maven, VUE, Eclipse, IntelliJ

C#, Udemy

I successfully completed an online C# course on Udemy, which provided comprehensive training in C# programming. The course covered essential topics such as C# syntax, object-oriented programming principles, data types, control structures, and more. Additionally, I gained hands-on experience in building C# applications, including desktop and web-based projects. This course equipped me with a strong foundation in C# development, enhancing my programming skills and knowledge in software development.

C++, Udemy

I am currently enrolled in a C++ course, which is being conducted through an online platform. This course is designed to cover a wide range of C++ programming concepts, including C++ syntax, object-oriented programming principles, data structures, algorithms, and software development practices. I am actively gaining experience in building C++ applications and developing problem-solving skills through various coding assignments and projects. This course is enhancing my proficiency in programming and preparing me for a successful career in software development.

Additional Info

Languages:

English – Native Swedish – Native Japanese – Basic

Hobbies: Traveling, PC tech, figure model painting, hiking, games.	